I haven't been to Sephora in like a
year. So, I finally went today and I
bought a lot. I paid for it, don't
worry, but let's do a haul. A lot of my
things were out, so I got a bunch of new
things that I'm so excited. First thing
I got was the Glow Recipe toner. Mine is
so water down and I'm so excited for
this. I'm going to open it because Oh my
gosh, I just I'm so excited because I
haven't had one of these in so long.
It's so milky now. Mine is so water
down. Oh my gosh, and the packaging
inside is watermelon. I love. And then I
got the Sol de Janeiro 48 water lotion.
I don't really know why it's called
water lotion, but you know, whatever. I
got two brushes because I really needed
them. Also, each of these were $35. They
were the cheapest ones.
And then I got a Gisou hair perfume and
I got a lot
of makeup. Okay, it's not a lot, but
it's
I got a Makeup Mario blush in pale
petal. I got a contour or cream bronzer
stick. I got a Summer Fridays lip liner
and a lip stain. I got a mascara
and then a new concealer because mine is
not my shade anymore because I got
tanner.
Anyways, that's my haul. Make sure you
go check out my other videos cuz I'm
going to do a haul Target, Five Below,
Ulta, and other stores. Okay, bye guys.